Bunny Lacey
2014 Frazer Pl Unit A, Madison, WI 53713
920.227.3168
slacey@wisc.edu
https://bunnylacey.github.io/burrow/

## **SUMMARY**

A passionate and creative software engineer with a drive to deliver quality solutions for web and computer applications. Demonstrable success developing in new and evolving technologies. Ability to work and communicate proactively in a team environment. Experience operating in fast paced and changing environments.

## **SKILLS**

- Object Oriented Programming
- AGILE/SCRUM
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Adobe Creative Suite

- Full Stack Development
- User Interface Design
- C, C++, C#, Java, Python, SQL
- WebGL, OpenGL, OpenCV

## **EXPERIENCE**

115 Fighter Wing, Madison, WI, September 2015 – September 2016 Self-Assessment Program Manager, Office of Inspector General

- Authored squadron level guidelines for complying with Air Force Inspection System directives.
- Provided training of the Management Internal Control Toolset.
- Performed contextual inquiries to identify MICT program shortfalls.
- Developed MICT managing and auditing program in Excel using Visual Basic for Applications.
- Saved Air Force significant costs from acquiring enterprise software to solve program shortfalls.
- Awarded Air Force Achievement medal for work on Air Force Inspection System.

128 Air Control Squadron, Camp Douglas, WI, July 2010 – April 2017 Staff Sergeant, Ground Radar Systems Craftsman

- Maintained mechanical and electrical components of various radar systems and subsystems.
- Task trained and evaluated performance of junior Airmen.
- Deployed in support of Operation Enduring Freedom 2012 2013.
- 2013 Air National Guard Ground Radar Airman of the Year.

Bean Creative, Alexandria, VA, August 2007 – July 2010 Interactive Software Developer

- Performed software prototyping, testing, and consultation.
- Primary developer for JavaScript/ActionScript projects and LAMP applications.

- Created/Edited various media using production software such as Photoshop and Illustrator.
- 2008 Adobe Max Finalist for work on PBS Kids Word World interactive website.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science University of Wisconsin Madison September 2011 – December 2017

Bachelor of Science, Digital Art and Design
Full Sail University
September 2005 – August 2007
Course Director Award in Entertainment Business